Talk about the structures of marriage.
People love to talk about that type of shit.
I want to hear you talk about it.
I mean, marriage is literally invented as the slavery of women.
They called slavery of black people, chattel slavery, and they called the slavery of women
marriage.
Really?
Like, that's just...
It was made up to trade women as property because patriarchy happened first at the end
of the Neolithic era when people started farming.
Certain people were like, well, if we farm, then we need private property to say what
land is mine so that I know what food is mine.
And therefore, what we were doing before where people had kids and everybody raised
everybody, it's like, now I need to know what children are mine because I need to know who
I can make work this farm and who I'm responsible to feed.
And in order to know what children is mine, I need to know what woman is mine.
And boom, you get marriage.
And then that goes to Europe and then gets Christianized and then they use Christianity
as a weapon, as a sword to hold to all of our necks to colonize the entire planet.
The normative culture that we're all treated like is just regular when it's actually very
new.
I mean, Brandi and Monica knew about it because they said the boy is mine.